

Akshatha Mahadevachary

RPA DEVELOPER



+91-7353986850



akshatha.m22@gmail.com



Technical Profile

- Blue Prism
- ABBYY Flexi Capture
- Python
- Core Java
- My SQL
- HTML/CSS

Competencies

- Technical Analysis
- Teamwork and Collaboration
- Product development
- Organization and Time Management
- Motivation to Learn

Languages

- English
- Kannada

Certification

Blue Prism Accredited Developer (AD01):

https://www.youracclaim.com/badge s/78eabd27-19db-438e-b6f7-4f8d086f98be Detail-oriented team player with 5+ years of Experience and strong organizational skills. Ability to handle multiple projects simultaneously with a high degree of accuracy. Organized and dependable candidate successful at managing multiple priorities with a positive attitude. Willingness to take on added responsibilities to meet team goals.

Work History:

2022-07 – Current

Systems Analyst

Speridian Technologies, Bangalore

- Performed system analysis, documentation, testing, implementation, and user support for platform transitions.
- Gathered requirements and performed gap analysis through design workshops with users.
- Self-inspired professional. Strives to complete all assigned duties on schedule and Actively demonstrates commitment by maintaining a predictable and consistent work schedule.

2021-04 – 2022-07

Application Development Senior Analyst

Accenture Solutions pvt Itd, Bangalore

- Identified and acquired appropriate third-party solutions to integrate into development processes.
- Formulated strategies for application development framework creation and developmental processes.
- Defined project-wide performance metrics such as developmental milestones, timeline goals and required completion dates.
- Solve day to day issues arising while running automated processes and provide timely resolutions.
 GAP analysis for existing use cases in production.
 Optimize the performance of the applications, debugging the errors encountered by analyzing the logs and other dependent applications.

2018-03 – 2021-03

Systems Engineer

Tata Consultancy Services pvt ltd, Bangalore

- Design, develop and deploy Robotic Process Automation (RPA) solutions using a variety of software tools, design principles and conventions, centered around Blue Prism as the primary RPA software.
- Document the proposed solution which includes a definition of the user interfaces, functional processes, and data within the proposed system.

Education:

2013-08 **–** 2017-06

Bachelor of Engineering in Computer & Science
Visvesvaraya Technological University, Belgaum, Karnataka